你说的我很喜欢
I think I like what you mean here.
关于圣杯之战有很多故事
There are many stories about the quest of the holy grail
这次,圣杯将寻找新的英灵
This time, the holy grail is looking for somes heroes
召唤到“棋盘”之上
Summoned to a chessboard
众神的无尽之战
The endless game of god
但是如今一切改变了
But lately that has changed
英灵们将终结圣杯之战
And But these heroes will end the holy grail war
“千年平衡”僵持的终结
The end of the millenium balance
本字幕由夜桜字幕组制作
翻译:お兄様
时轴:晚风
校对&压制:雪夜
我不知道这是哪,但我知道这绝不是现实世界.
I don't know what is this place but I know this isn't the real world
呵呵 当然不是了
hahaha, no doubt after that long trip.
你看看头顶
ahahaha, ok, just look at the sky,
我们貌似被牵扯到这个游戏中了.
you know what, we seemed to be involved in a game.
你啥意思
What is the meaning of this?
大家请听我说.
Everybody, please listen to me.
我是圣杯守护者,但是圣杯已经坏了
I am the guardian of the holy grail, but the holy grail was recently broken.
圣杯之战平衡已经被破坏
The endless balance of the game has been shuttered.
混沌将会肆虐
Chaos will spread all over the world.
这是什么垃圾玩意儿
Wh\at is this garbage.
它把我们拉进去了
It's pulling us in.
他会把我们传送到需要我们的地方
This will send us to places we're needed. .
这所有的幻象都在让我激动难耐
All of these illusions are intriguing me.
啊,我去
Er, damn.
她和圣杯的联系被激活了
Her connection to the holy grail has been summoned.
因为他是ruler级别的servant,所以她没有master来补魔
Because she is a ruler class servant,
she doesn't have a master to rely on for additional mana supply.
以圣杯现在的情况来说,她已经无法维持肉体形态并完成使命
With the holy grail as it is right, she won't be able to maintain her physical form and complete the mission.
如果她消失了,那么新的圣杯和无尽的战争又要开始
If she disappears, the grail and endless war will follow.
只有一个方法给她补魔了
There's only one way to supply her with the mana she needs.
啪啪啪
A sexual fluids transfer.
快来玩啊 宝贝儿
Hum, come quickly baby.
她新来的？我以前没见过这蓝发妞
She new here? I haven't seen the girl with blue hair before.
来嘛小哥哥们,你们会爽的
Come on guys, you know you're gonna have fun.
哦诶,小婊子,让我看看你的美臀
Ohe, chicks, let me look at your sweet ass.
来快活啊 来啊
come on baby, come on
啪一晚 啪一晚
Hooker doesn't rest tonight. Hooker doesn't rest tonight.
等下,我好像看到什么了,把车停了
I just saw something! An Outlandish Costume girl!
下车,我们要看仔细点
top the car, we need to look closer.
我喜欢这婊子,她像个洋娃娃
i like this shit, she's like a beautiful doll or something.
把她弄起来
get her up quickly
哦,别急 别急
oh no, wait, wait, ok?
你应该给我们组团价
You should give us a special price for group.
等一下等一下,先听我说.
wait a minute and listen to me.
不群P,我只和一个啪,一次一个
no gang bang ,i only do with one person, one on one.
呵呵,他们是什么玩意,一群傻逼罢了
huh, what are that, kids? just a bunch of assholes.
快点,你他么在浪费我时间吗
Hurry up, you are wasting our time.
健硕的小哥哥,你好像失忆了,我可以和你们群P,1V4
you, the strong man, it seems that you have lost your memories, i can handle you all at he same time, four one one.
只有我可以
i'll be the one.
好的
ok
你准备好了吗,咱们走
are you ready, let's go
好的，你可赚大了
All right,you did get a really good deal.
我好激动呀
i''m so excited
看这cos女的大屁股
Look at the cosplay girl's big butt.
你个小坏蛋
you little scum.
你摸起来真软
it feels soft to touch.
她真奇怪
she'll feel odd
她好像不是一般妓女
she's not like an ordinary hooker.
快跑
keep running .
别管我,跑
don't worry about me, just gone.
我不能丢下你
i can't leave you behind
我能搞定这些僵尸
i will solve these zombies.
那就按你说的来吧
have it your way.
我是魔界骑士英格丽德
I'm the Hells Knight Ing-!!!!ah
我怎么会被这些弱小怪物伤害
can't i be hurt by such weak monsters.
别碰我
don't touch me.
操
damn
贞德
Joan
不 我拒绝
no i refuse
你听我说
listen to me
你咋能提这么龌龊的建议
how dare you propose such a thing.
别碰我
don't touch me
我拒绝和你说话
i refuse to speak with.
就算你这么说,我们还是必须重构你的肉体,在...（一切太迟之前）
even if you say that we have to reform your look somehow, before.......
死一边去
go away.
将是大军没完没了了
this army of zombies is endless.
操
damn
别扯我手臂
stop grabbing my arm.
我的腿没力了,越来越多僵尸在上我
My legs grows weak as more and more zombies cling to my body.
我怕是要输了
i'm going to lose here.
我不管 我拒绝和别的人做
i don't care, i refuse to do that with other man .
好吧,其实我也不想这么做,但我们必须做点什么
be nice, look, i don't want to do this either, but we've got to do something.
好吧 我投降
ok i surrender
你再跑一个试试
you come and run you're dear now?
看起来你已经做好决定了
it seems that you have made a decision.
好的,打开我看看
yes, then open it.
哦 真不错
哇啊
不做不行啊
Since it must be done
来啊 杰拉德
come on Gerrard.
我接受你的提议 女妖王
I accept your offer, Banshee Queen.
对她好点
Please take care of her
谢谢你们的神圣种子（WTF）
thank you for bringing your holy seed.
上帝保佑我们
Might god light shine upon us.
对她好点,谢谢你们
You have my thanks!
好吧,你去吧
ok you go.
她不是个神圣修女吗
isn't she supposed to be a holy sister.
holy shit, look at this.
我勒个去 看这儿
她再也不是谁的神圣处女了
she won't be a holy virgin for anyone anymore.
她进入状态了
she's getting on
她的“圣堂”打开了
Her holy temple is opening..
太令人激动了 我等不及了
oh it's so exciting i can't wait
让我看看你们的渴望你们的性致,来粗暴的玩我的身体,快给我
show me your passion your desires, use my body roughly, be merciless be rude to me, give it all to me.
操 你这就有点过分了
fuck You just made it personal now..
看样子你已经做好准备了 我尊重你的选择
you're the woman who's ready for everything, i respect your choice.
游戏开始
let the games begin.
你知道该做什么
you know what to do.
把我裤子脱了
take off my pants.
好姑娘,我很久没洗澡了,大屌肯定贼脏贼臭,来帮我舔干净
good girl, i haven't showered in a wile i must have built up a lot of smegma so clean it for me.
把你的脏手拿开,别揉我奶头
Urgg,  Keep your gross finger out of my clit. Stop crushing my tits.
这大屌要把我玩坏的
This horse cock will break me apart.
我要插了
i'll come in
插你妹啊
Of course not.
我要你的屌
i want your big dick
想让我插,你知道要先干什么
If you want me to put it in. You know what to do first.
乐意之至 巫师
That will be my pleasure, Witcher..
特大新闻,一个神秘女子和一群cos成古代士兵的男子在海边悬崖上群交 也不知道他们怎么爬上这么陡峭的海边悬崖的
Breaking news. A mysterious woman and a group of men dressed as ancients soldiers are engaged in group sex on the top of a sea cliff. Nobody knows how theses people reach such a steep place
据专家表示,这可能是某种神秘仪式,但目前为止没有组织生成为此负责
According to our expert, that might be some kind of ritual, but so far no known organization has claimed to be behinds theses acts.
你们就这点本事吗
Is that all you got, you weakling ?
不管怎样 我绝不屈服
I won't yield, no matter what.
我不屈服*2
I won't yield, I won't yield
我绝不向这么低等的种族屈服
I'm not going to submit to such an inferior races.
嘿,我有个主意
hey, i think i've got a idea.
像个RBQ
looks like a charm.
你也不是很牛逼嘛,我要射了,别停,
Not so tough now, aren't you?  I am about to cum. Keep up the pace,
吞下去
swallow it all !
好了伙计们,接下来看你们怎么玩这个婊子了
Okay guys, now let see how you handle this bitch.
终于到我了
It's my turn finally! .
把我的屌舔干净
Lick my dick clean
把她弄过去
Let's lie her down there
哦,这些屌都是给我的？不介意我自助吧
Oh, are these all for me ? Well don’t mind if i help myself
她在看镜头
she's looking at the camera.
停,我不行了
Please, stop i can't continue.
我脸摔到地上了,你这傻逼怪物
Oww, I landed on my face, you stupid red monster.
不要了,让我休息下
don't, let me rest.
你们还没操够吗
haven't you had enough.
被这么多人啪过还这么紧,我再操也没事吧
still so tight after so many huh? no matter if i do
我能感受到别的英灵在完成他们的使命
I can fell the others, accomplishing their fate.
为了圣杯和其他人 我必须坚持
I must endure this, i must continue for the grail and the others
啊哈,这次之后你就要被玩坏了
aha you're gonna  be a sloppy mess after this one.
它们会杀了她
They are going to kill her !
离开她
get off her.
拖住它们
hold them off.
叶奈法
Yennefer
Yennefer！！！
干得不错,再坚持一会
You’re holding well. Keep going for a while.
好了,女士,吸收神圣能量吧
now, ma'am, holy power to absorb.
你的苦难刚刚开始
your sloppy second is here.
看起来你伤全好了
looks like you're fully healed
是的 这个治愈魔法很有效
yes this magic is very effective.
我还记得你这声音,圣杯肯定已经复原了
I remembered that voice back then. The Holy Grail must be restored.
恩 现在咱俩有点尴尬了
This is a little awkward.
你的大屌已经饥渴难耐
You're loaded for bear, and just itching to roar
别方,我来帮你解决
Do not worry. Let me take care of this.
过来
come on
现在它进去了
and it's going in now.
哦 你的屌好舒服
Oh, you feel great inside me.
我没想到你活这么好
I didn't think you would be so good
你的一颦一笑
the ways you move, your smiles, your wits,
对我而言无可取代
that's too much
你虽然不说话 我也能感受到你的屌在颤动
Although you do not speak, I can feel your dick's twitching too
我能感受到你
I can feel you all!!ahhhh!!!!
非英语的呻吟
你准备好来第二发了吗
are you ready for round two
原谅我 至黑大人
Oh Black sama, forgive
给我 给我大屌
Give me more ahhh big dick
给我屌
give me dick
那晚夜空被万千星辰点亮
The sky was speckled with millions of stars.
星光在你脸上闪耀
The stars are shining in your face.
你急什么,你知道我现在很虚
Why are you in such a hurry ? I'm still worn out you know.
人家就想要嘛
i really want it.
这 我有个cos的小姐姐
Here, i got a cosplay girl.
这婊子像疯了一样爱啪啪啪
That bitch likes it like crazy
你们闪开 我来
I'll take it from here. no slacking off
操 她真的很享受这个
Damn, she is really into this.
她的逼不是这个世界的
Her ass is out of this world
我简直是一流女星
i am such a movie star
来呀 大块头  操我
Come on big guy, pound me right.
玩坏我 操我啊 用力
Ravish me, pound me, fuck me harder
操我 操我
treat me like a whore.
好的宝贝 那就是你想要的
that's what you want baby.
让我们来满足你
Let's plug that filthy month of your.
滚开 傻逼
keep off you're perrot
别盯着她看 明白？
don't look her in the eye understand.
用力 用力 操我 操我
fuck me harder,treat me like a whore.
你插得我好深
you're reaching so far into my pussy.
啊啊 你好大 好大
ahah you're so big you're huge.
啊 我要疯了 我受不了了
i'm going crazing i can't stand it
喂我 喂我 拿你们的大屌喂我的骚逼
yes yes feed me, feed my pussy with you cock.
你不喝干我每一滴精液我就不让你歇着
No way, i am letting you breathing until you drink my spunk.
操 cos女 你真是性爱女王
Damn, cosplay girl, you are a sex queen.
这婊子越来越有感觉了
The bitch is starting to feel it.
啊 好舒服
oh so good
发生什么了
what the hell is going on.
还在录像
hum . It is still recording
攫取你们的灵魂
Soul Drain absorb the soul
这些能量已经足够复原圣杯了
these energies are enough to restore the holy grail.
谢谢你们 你们所有人 不论你们身处何方
Thank you, all of you. Wherever you are
还没完呢
This isn’t over
欢迎来到恶魔世界 但丁
Welcome to the demon world Dante
你好啊 来啊
hi~~~~come on
来打我啊 哈哈哈
Then go for it, I'm right here.hahaha
你是恶魔 我是恶魔猎手
You're a demon. And I'm a demon hunter
那你来啊 我就在这
Then go for it, I'm right here.hahaha
真有意思
It's interesting
小帅哥 怎么样？
how's that sound handsome.
接招小帅哥 我简直控制不住自己了
take that pretty boy. i just can't keep control myself
剑对你无效 看起来你喜欢在腿上开洞
swords aren't working, looks like you like being pumped in the leg
女王 逮到你了（直译 你的屁股是我的了）
your ass is mine, my queen.
你可以享受更多 只要你乖乖的
you can have more than  that if you're a good boy.
看来我的屁股也让你兴奋
i see that the butts excites you too.
我听说过你们淫魔,用性快感掌控凡人
i heard about the succubus the sexual pleasure that gets the mortals
我倒想看看你有什么本事
and i be like to see what you got to offer.
好 让我们来看看你是否和传说的一样厉害
ok let's see if you live up to the legend.
趴在地上,女王
get down on the ground queen
让我来教你怎么使用我的大宝剑
let me show you how to handle my big sword.
什么 你个小鸡鸡
what, you cocky little...
我够牛逼 我能受得了
i'm strong i can take it
好了 你也爽过了 现在是时候换个位置了
alright you had your fun, now how about a little roller versa
从我身上起开,我要把你重新打回地狱
get the fuck off me i'm gonna send you back to hell.
重回地狱？哦 亲爱的 你已经在地狱了
back to hell? oh darling, you're already there.
你 你 你干嘛 你认真·····
what the, what fuck are you doing. are you really...
美酒啊
like wine
双重麻烦咯
double trouble
你们的罪恶足以让你们下地狱
the sin dispose you straight to hell
don't struggle pet, we'll clean you up nicely.
别挣扎 小乖乖 我们会好好帮你打扫干净